Every time I walk
Every time I run
Every time I move
As always, for us
Every time I look
Every time I love
Every time I hope
As always, for us
My two feet walk willingly, anywhere
내 두 발은 선뜻 걸어, anywhere
Mis pies caminan sin dudar, anywhere
僕の両足は軽やかに歩く、anywhere
我的双脚欣然前行 anywhere
J in the air
For the path I’m on to become one of hope, I give my all
進む道が希望になってほしくて、僕は敢えて
가는 길이 희망이 되고자 하여, 나 구태여
Espero que mi camino sea la esperanza, insisto
要让前路成为希望 我一定
Even my walk was made of your love and your faith
To repay you even from afar, just like a butterfly
Te lo recompenso, me convierto en una mariposa, aunque sea a lo lejos
恩返しをする、遥か遠くからでも蝶になって
보답을 해, 저 멀리서라도 나비가 되어
再遥远也变成蝴蝶 去回报
Now just walk lightly, whenever you want
Go on hopefully, wherever you walk
In these streets imbued with someone’s breath
誰かの息吹が宿っている街並み
누군가의 숨이 깃들어 있는 거리
El camino impregnado con la respiración de alguien
街上弥漫着谁的气息
I leave my soul and my eternity
僕の魂と永遠を込めるよ
내 영혼과 영원을 담을게
Lo llenaré con mi alma y eternidad
承载我的灵魂与永恒
Everywhere (I’ll be)
Every time I walk
Every time I run
Every time I move
As always, for us
Every time I look
Every time I love
Every time I hope
As always, for us
(On the street, I’m still)
Every time I walk
Every time I run
Every time I move
As always, for us
Every time I look
Every time I love
Every time I hope
As always, for us
(On the street, I’m still)
All hail the mighty survivor of hell
Plopped down from heaven to sell
Holy water that I scooped from the well
Fought tooth and a nail,
Just to prevail mongst it’s ruthless
As I move through the field
Feelin worried
In a hurry like a 2 minute drill
To make a couple mil
Off a lucrative deal
Selling train of thought,
Name a artist who could derail
You’ll never see it like a nigga hula hoopin in jail
I got a friend smart as fuck, but he stupid as hell
He swear that God ain’t real
Since it ain’t no way to prove it his self
As if the universe ain’t enough
As if the volcanoes ain’t erupt
As if the birds don’t chirp
As if a trillion nerves don’t work in the human body
Who would I be?
Without the creator of this theater
Beside me to gently guide me?
Somedays I wonder if I need to pick a different hobby
I’m deep in with this rappin
It’s all a nigga know
I never didn’t nothin better, it’s hard to let it go
But like a father, watching his daughter, walk down the altar,
With tears in his eyes, you gotta let her grow
And so I shall, but first I been honing my style
Coldest around, with more quotables than what the quota allows
You see a top 10 list I see a Golden Corral, nigga
As the moon jumps over the cow
I contemplate if I should wait to hand over the crown
And stick around for a bit longer
I got a strange type of hunger
The more I eat the more it gets stronger,
The more it gets stronger
I said the more it gets stronger
j-hope
Cole World
Every time I walk
Every time I run
Every time I move
As always, for us
Every time I look
Every time I love
Every time I hope
As always, for us
(On the street, I’m still)
Every time I walk
Every time I run
Every time I move
As always, for us
Every time I look
Every time I love
Every time I hope
As always, for us
(On the street, I’m still)